gihosoft.com 2018-03-06

# Gihosoft Privacy Policy - Gihosoft Studio

Gihosoft.com respects your privacy and we are dedicated to protecting personal information. All information as well as requests we collected are only for defined purchases, and we not sell, share or rent the information to other person or organization in ways different from what is disclosed in the following privacy statement.

## What Information We Collect & How We Use It

Gihosoft.com do not collect personal information from visitors to our website, when browsing web pages, downloading software from our site. We do not collect email addresses from people who send us Email directly. Gihosoft only reply your questions or queries to corresponding email address for providing better customer service.

### 1\. Registration information

All programs on Gihosoft.com are free to try without registering. If you want to register our software for fully use, you will need to provide us with correct license information such as your email address. The information is only used to identify your software license that it will never appear in public place of our website.

### 2\. Payment information

The third-party payment partner we choose is the worldwide leading company in shareware distribution and online payment. When you place an order on our website, your email, full name, street address, city, state, postal code, country and credit card number will be required for completing the transaction. The payment is finished on the third-party payment system MyCommerce.com for the sake of providing you safe and fast online purchase. We only keep customer name and email address to provide customers better technical support.

### 3\. Contact information

When you contact Gihosoft team, we will keep a record of the communication content to help solve your queries or questions more efficiently. We may use the contact information to inform you about our software new updates and changes.

## Sharing Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to any third-party for any reason, unless such disclosure is necessary and you have given us the permission.

## About Cookies

Gihosoft.com uses cookies on our website to collect information about website traffic. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. The cookies is only used to track page popularity, traffic flows and etc to enhance the user experience of our website. You may choose to refuse cookies in web browser.

## Changes to This Policy

Gihosoft has the discretion to change this privacy policy any time without notification to you. Any changes will be posted here. We encourage users to visit this page to become aware of updates.

## Contact Gihosoft

If you have any question about this privacy statement, or queries about our software, or suggestions about us, please contact us at: support#gihosoft.com ( please replace ” # ” with ” @ ” ).
